<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Log Book Application</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="home_info_text">Log booking like never ever before. It\'s now easy to document the most important moments of internship in a fun way without worrying about paperwork!</string>
    <string name="home_more_info_text">For Lecturers, For Industrial Supervisors, For you!
A Computer Science Project, From Kaduna State University</string>
    <string name="title_activity_user_home">user_home</string>

    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="title_activity_daily_attendance">daily_attendance</string>
    <string name="title_activity_weekly_progress_report">weekly_progress_report</string>
    <string name="title_activity_code_of_conduct">Code Of Conduct</string>
    <string name="large_text">
        "STUDENTS INDUSTRIAL WORK EXPERIENCE SCHEME (SIWES) CODE OF CONDUCT FOR STUDENTS ON SIWES.\n\n"

        "Students are to obey all rules and regulations of th organization to which they are attached "
        "for practical experience. Defaults should be reported by organization to the institution promptly."
        "Students dressing at all times must be modest, net and in good. It should also conform to the "
        "dictates of their profession where applicable.\n\n"

        "Students are to be punctual for duty every working day. They are to resume and close from work "
        "at the time officially scheduled by the organization. They are to sign a daily entry exit "
        "attendance register throughout the period of attachment.\n\n"

        "Absence from duty for cogent reasons must be properly documented and approved by the Industry Based Supervisor ".
        "Otherwise absence without cogent reasons and/or proper approval will attract appropriate disciplinary action.\n\n"

        "The organization reserves the right to reject or send student back to the university in "
        "case of any misconduct or act(s)incompatible with its objectives, that of the SIWES, or the Kaduna State University\n\n"

        "All forms given out to the students must be filled and submitted to the appropriate office(s) at the appropriate "
        "times dring the SIWES programme.\n\n"

        "Students must fill their logbooks on schedule and submit to their industry-based supervisor at the close of the work "
        "every Friday for the duration of attachment. It is the student's responsibility to ensure logbooks are filled as "
        "appropriate. Studnets must weeks three typed and appropriately bound copies of their SIWES Report two weks after returning "
        "to the University at the end of the perid of attachment.\n\n"

        "Any student found to have contravened any of the items listed above and contained in the job guidelines, will be disciplined "
        "appropriately."


    </string>
</resources>
